Yuki-chan, please stand up for a moment.
ゆきちゃん、ちょっと立ってみて
Yuki-chan, have you lost weight?
ゆきちゃん、痩せた?
You've lost weight, definitely.
痩せたよね、絶対
That's why I lost weight.
だから、痩せたって
Turn around for a moment.
一瞬回ってみて
It's super stylish.
超スタイルいいじゃん
It's constricted.
くびれちゃってんじゃん
Is this a constriction?
これくびれなの?
Let your butt dig into your pants a little.
お尻、ちょっと、パンツ食い込ませて
I don't like that, I don't like that.
嫌だ、それ嫌だ
why?
なんで?
I don't like that.
それ嫌だ
Just like that, for those who are a little virgin,
そのまんま、そのまんまちょっと童貞さんの方に、
Hey, let me show you your ass.
ちょっと、お尻見せてあげて
Oh, is that so?
え、そういうこと?
Something like this?
こういうこと?
What should we do about that?
そういうこと、どうすか?
Ah, beautiful.
あ、きれい
Well then, you can touch it a little.
じゃあ、ちょっと触ってもいいっすよ
Please touch me, then.
触ってあげてください、そしたら
What do you think?
感想はどうすか?
soft.
柔らかい
It seems that it is.
だそうです
Well then, Yuki-chan, you can sit down.
じゃあ、ゆきちゃん、座っていいっすよ
It seems that it is.
だそうです
Well then, it's like this.
じゃあ、まあね、こんな感じで
I can tell that you're a little nervous,
ちょっと緊張してるっていうのがだいぶ伝わってるから、
I thought I'd do some different things with the teacher as well.
先生もね、交えて、ちょっといろいろと行為をしていこうかなと思
Yeah.
うん で
good?
いい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
So.
それで
Okay.
よし
Yuki-chan, today's underwear.
ゆきちゃん、今日の下着さ
What is this?
なにこれ?
Isn't it super cute?
超かわいくない?
Well, there are two.
てか、二つや、やば
It's great.
最高にいいよ
OK, let's do it then.
OK、じゃあやっていこうか
Well, thank you very much.
じゃあ、よろしくお願いします
Please sit a little closer.
もうちょっと近く座ってもらって
You've never been kissed, have you?
キスしたことないんでしょ?
yes.
はい
Would you like to try it?
してみたい?
yes.
はい
Yuki-chan, are you okay?
ゆきちゃん、大丈夫?
Okay.
いいよ
Yuki-chan, by the way, how many children are there?
ゆきちゃんさ、ちなみにさ、何人目?
Chew.
チューするの
The 6th person?
6人目?
I don't understand, that's it.
わからないよ、そんな
Hey, I understand.
ちょっとね、わかった
That's enough.
もういいよ
Well then, let's face each other and have a look.
じゃあ、向き合って、チューしてみようか
First of all, do what you want.
自分もまず、したいように
I won't say anything anymore, so just give me a chew.
もう、何も言わないから、チューまでして
That's not all.
それだけじゃないでしょ
more.
もっと
Chew more.
もっとチューしてよ
Yuki-chan, look up a little.
ゆきちゃん、ちょっと顔上げて
Well then, Yuki-chan, please lead the way.
じゃあ、ゆきちゃん、リードしてあげて
Oh, me?
あ、私が?
What if it becomes like a chew?
チューぐらいになったら?
If it's Chu, you can go.
チューだったら、いけるでしょ
What if it becomes a normal kiss?
普通のキスになったら?
Yeah, just a normal kiss is fine.
うん、普通のキスでいい
real?
ほんと?
A word of reflection.
感想一言
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Well then, I want to meet you soon.
じゃあ、そろそろ会いたい
I miss you.
会いたい
I want to meet you.
会いたいよね
I'll see for myself.
自分でじゃあ、見よっか
Let me take off your bra.
ブラ外してあげて
This is the first time I've taken off my bra.
ブラ外すのも初めてだよね
early.
早い
It's early, take it off.
早いね、外すの
Well then, take a good look.
じゃあ、しっかり見て
Let's touch it with both hands.
触ってみよっか、両手で
You don't have to be conscious of the camera,
カ メラとか意識しないでいいから、
As you like.
自分が好きなように
How do you touch it?
触り方どう?
Would you like to touch it?
触ってみけど?
Touching it for the first time.
初めて触る
first time?
初めて?
You want to touch it more, right?
もっと触りたいでしょ
Well, it's better here too.
なんかさ、ここも上回り
Touch it as you like.
自分が好きなように触って
You really don't have to be conscious of the camera.
ほんとカメラとか、意識しないでいいよ
I want to touch it more and chew it.
も っと触りながらチューとかしたい
It's early again.
また早い
Do as you like.
好きなようにして
Riki-chan too.
りきちゃんも
Just a little bit is fine, this is fine.
ちょっとだけでいいから、これいいよ
Now, put your left hand around Riki-chan's shoulder.
じゃあ、左手をりきちゃんの肩に回して
You're used to it.
慣れてるね
Just chew.
チューするだけでいい
Riki-chan, can you put your tongue in it?
りきちゃん、ベロ入れてあげることできる?
Yeah.
うん
Can you do tongue chewing?
ベロチューできる?
Belochu.
ベロチュー
Lower it.
下げて
I'm getting excited.
興奮してきた
Well, let's take it off.
じゃあ、脱ごうか
Before that, you can undress Yuki-chan as well.
その前、ゆきちゃんも脱がしてからでもいいし、
please.
どうぞ
If you're embarrassed, can you take it off first?
恥ずかしかったら、先に脱げてもらう?
Well then, let me take it off myself.
じゃあ、自分で脱がしてあげて
At the same time, take it off yourself.
ついでに自分で脱げて
Give me Bowser.
クッパーちょうだい
Then, sit in front of Yuki-chan.
じゃあ、ゆきちゃんの前に座って
Let's take a look
見てみよう
mosquito.
か
Look carefully.
し っかり見て
Don't look at me.
俺のことを見るんじゃなくて
Riki-chan's.
り きちゃんの
Look at Yuki-chan's tongue.
ゆきちゃんのベロちゃんと見て
Shall I try licking it?
舐めてみようか
You've never licked it, have you?
舐めたことないでしょ
Is it easier to lick it a little earlier?
もうちょっと前のほうが舐めやすい?
It's kind of dry.
なんか、乾燥ある
Quite soft.
結構、柔らかい
soft?
柔らかい?
What does it taste like?
味は?
taste?
味?
I don't know much.
あんまり知らない
He's a good boy, this one.
いい子だよ、この子は
Do you want to touch it?
触 ってみたい?
Can I touch it?
触っていい?
Isn't it good?
いいよね?
Yuki-chan, okay?
ゆきちゃん、いいよね?
Tell me if it hurts.
痛かったら言ってね
If it hurts, tell me.
痛かったら言うんだよ
Should I put my finger inside?
指、中に入れたらいい?
Can I enter?
入れられる?
Be careful not to scratch it with your nails.
爪で引っかかないようにね
I'm going to put it in this paint.
この塗装の中に、自分が入れるんだよ
Looks like I'll be able to get in.
入れられそう
Are you okay?
大丈夫か?
Did it hurt?
痛かった?
If it hurts, tell me.
痛かったら言うんだよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Does it hurt a little?
ちょっと痛い?
Did you have feelings?
気持ちがあった?
it hurts.
痛い
Tell me if it hurts.
痛かったら言って
Well then,
じゃあ、
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Do you think you can continue?
続 けられそう?
Wait a minute, wait.
ちょっと待って待って
Are you going to cry?
泣いちゃうの?
That's it.
そんな
stop?
止める?
Can I continue?
続けていい?
this.
これ
Can I continue?
続けていい?
Impossible?
無理?
Did you add blood?
血入れた?
it hurts?
痛い?
Then, can I make a loss?
そしたらさ、 損入できる?
Can I make a loss?
損入していい?
Impossible?
無理?
Seriously?
マジ?
Hey, you have beautiful boobs,
ちょっと、 せっかくおっぱいきれいだから、
Can I have breasts?
おっぱいにしていい?
Impossible?
無理?
Yeah.
うん
It hurt a little.
ちょっと痛かったね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
But, I won't force you to do anything.
でもさ、強制的なことしないから
Yeah.
うん
Just once, then, virgin, please take a short break.
ちょっと一回、じゃあ童貞さん、ちょっと一回休憩してもらって
Wait a minute, actor.
ちょっと、じゃあ男優さん
With the teacher?
先生と?
Teacher and player change.
先生と、選手交代
選手交代
If so, can you feel safe?
だったら安心できる?
Okay.
いいよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
OK, let's do that then.
OK、じゃあそれでやろうか
yes.
はい
It hurt a little, didn't it?
ちょっと痛かったよね
Sorry.
ごめんね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Sorry for earlier.
さっきごめんね
Yeah, it's okay.
うん、大丈夫
I can't put my fingers in it.
指とか入れないから
It's in a shape without sixes, so all you have to do is touch it.
シックスないのかたちで、 触るだけでいいから、
I want you to touch me.
触ってほしい
Look at your face.
顔、そっちほら
Again?
またか
I'll do that.
そうする
I want to put it in.
入れたいな
feeling.
気持ち
It's closed.
閉まってるね
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
I think I'll go if I keep going.
続けてたら行っちゃいそう
It's a little scary.
ちょっとやばい
Turn towards me, towards the broken back.
こっち向いて、背中折れの方に向けて
Sit down.
座って
Just sleep and stay that way.
寝るだけでそのまま
good
よい
Sho.
しょ
The back looks like it's going to go up.
バ ックが上がりそう
If you put it to sleep, it will close.
寝てあげると、閉まるんだね
Because I want to go soon.
そろそろ行きたいから
Shall I let you sleep?
寝てあげようか
Is it bad for middle school?
中ダメなんだっけ?
Yeah, it's bad.
うん、中ダメ
Well, I'll call it, okay?
じゃあ、かけちゃうけどいい?
I'll put it on my face.
顔にかけるね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Sorry, just a little.
ごめんね、ちょっとね
I felt hurt, though.
痛い思いもしちゃったけどね
Was it okay?
大丈夫だった?
See you soon, Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん、またね
Thank you again for today.
ありがとうね、今日もね
Bye bye.
バイバーイ